STANDARD FOR LIFE
As Wise Man Racine prays for the people in the name of Jesus Christ,
satan and his demons are exposed and the grip is loosed from their lives.
With just one touch from the Wise Man,
the satanic powers in the life of this young man are exposed.
He begins to show a violent display of outward frustration.
Let's watch the encounter.
Speak! Who are you?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Who are you?
I am from the deepest ocean.
Speak out! What have you done to him?
I have destroyed him.
How did you destroy him?
I have destroyed him since he was a child.
How many demonic powers do you have?
Many.
Fire, in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire all over your body!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
How did you enter him?
Since he was born.
What have you done to his career?
Nothing.
How do you operate, you demon?
I fly in the night and take all the beautiful ladies to the ocean.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Where are you from?
I am from the deepest ocean.
The deep ocean?
Yes.
What are you doing there?
I am the supreme commander.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
How many of you are in this body?
How many of you?
Many of us: the great king, the big, giant man. I am a bird; I am a fish. I command.
What have you done to his career?
Anything I want, I get.
I have all the powers.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What do you want from me?
What else have you done to him?
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak!
No!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
Speak out all the evil!
I will kill you!
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What have you done to the family?
I have destroyed everybody in the family.
How did you destroy them?
Nothing.
If I enter the family, nothing will work.
I will take all the money and cause problems in the family.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
How do you operate in this body, you evil spirit?
I stopped his education. Nobody in his family wants to see him.
They see him as an evil boy.
How many of you are in this body?
There are six of us.
Name them. Who?
We operate in the graves at night.
We operate in the ocean.
How do you operate in the ocean?
We take all of the beautiful ladies to the ocean.
Who are you in the ocean, you demon?
I am the mighty king. I command.
I sleep with any of my ladies in the ocean.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
What do you use him to do?
To destroy the ladies out there.
To destroy.
How? How do you destroy the ladies?
All the ladies I have sex with, I render them useless.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
They become one of us in the ocean.
What have you done to his father?
No father.
I am the king in the water.
What have you done to his mother?
I control all.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I am the biggest bird in the sky.
I operate in the air.
Manifestation of Evil Spirits
I operate in the sky.
I operate under the ground.
How do you operate under the ground?
As what?
I cause accidents.
How do you cause accidents?
I cause accidents to travellers.
How do you use these demonic powers in this body?
I have powers in my eyes, private parts, legs and hands.
How do you use the power in your hands?
When I greet you, I take all your luck. If you are a lucky man.
What about the power in your legs?
What do you use this power in your legs for?
I use it to go any miles that I want to.
And the power is in my eyes...
What about the power in your private part?
How do you use it?
If I have sex with any girl...
What happens to that person?
She will never get pregnant and her life will be useless.
For how long have you been tormenting this boy?
Since when he was nine years old.
Nine years old?
I entered him in his grandfather's house.
Many dead people.
How did you enter him?
I entered him through masturbation.
In the night, we have a big meeting with the dead.
Which meeting?
Meeting with the dead.
Anybody that dies in the family, I know.
You demon!
This body is not your temple!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ...
Holy Ghost FIRE all over your body!
FIRE!
You can see all the demonic powers in this body in the name of Jesus Christ!
Fire! All over your body.
Fire! In your heart.
Fire! In your mind.
Fire! In the name of Jesus Christ.
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Come out of you, in the name of Jesus Christ!
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Come out!
Out!
In Jesus' name!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
In the mighty name of Jesus Christ!
Out!
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Be free.
In Jesus' name.
Thank You, Lord.
Deliverance in Jesus' Name
Stand up.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
Come.
How are you?
I am fine.
Do you remember what you have said?
No, man of God.
That demon that was destroying your life and your career,
Jesus Christ has cast it out today.
You are free, give thanks to God.
Thank You, Jesus.
Thank You, Jesus. I am delivered and free.
Set Free in Jesus' Name
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel! (God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Shalom and the woman next to me is my mum.
We are from Cameroon.
I have no father. My father left me when I was very young.
He is from Israel.
The problem that brought me to The SCOAN was the problem of evil spirits.
I was possessed with evil spirits.
When I was very young, I grew up not having parental guidance.
I lived out of the home, living on the streets with bad friends,
attending night clubs, parties and all.
I have been sleeping with girls.
This whole thing started on a Sunday morning when I got into a bathroom to shower.
I heard a spirit speaking to me, telling me to touch my private part.
While I touched my private part, I felt some sensational powers like excitement inside of me.
I kept touching my private part up and down and I felt some enlightenment in my body.
That was masturbation.
I was very young. I was eight years old when I started masturbating.
My mum and I were living in my grandfather's house.
After starting masturbating, this spirit made me to do many evil things.
For example, the girls I go out with.
I would have sex with them for about six hours without stopping.
I came to realise that while having sex with them,
I am not the one doing it, it is the demon.
There was another person in me that was having sex with them in the room.
Sometimes after having sex with them, the ladies would approach me later
to tell me that they see themselves getting married to me in the dream.
They cannot get pregnant.
As I continued masturbating, I also realised that I had several powers in me.
With the powers, I could control anybody around me.
I had dominion over anybody out there.
I could say anything and you would listen to whatever I tell you.
With these powers in me, I controlled big people, elderly people.
Most of my mates were people much older than me.
I got involved in a bad life by doing scamming.
That is, I stole and lied to people on the internet, dubbing them of their money.
I got involved into scamming of many people all over the country, lieing to them, deceiving them,
and taking large amounts of money just for having fun with girls and going to night clubs.
I also got involved in a Facebook chat.
I would go online on the internet.
Whenever I go online with girls on the internet,
I would convince them to get naked online, including myself, and we would have sex online.
Sixty percent of our children today have offended God.
Their food is this internet.
Their partner is internet.
Their best friend is internet.
During this period of scamming and online chatting, I lived alone.
My mum was never at home with me.
My mum didn't know of any of the things I was doing.
I hid everything I was doing from her.
During the period of chatting with the naked girls online, I too would get naked.
The ladies would start touching their private parts and masturbating,
and I would do the same.
After doing that, I initiate them online.
They become part of my kingdom.
In my kingdom, I operate in the water.
Sometimes my spirit leaves me and I turn into a fish.
Then, I go to attend a meeting in the water.
This kept happening and when I go to the water,
I see beautiful girls.
Beautiful girls that are virgins.
They would be swimming in the water, looking at me with respect,
and treat me like a supreme or bigger person to them.
I also had the spirit of a bird. I could fly.
I always saw myself transforming into a big bird,
flying up in the sky and going to anywhere that I wanted to go.
Late in the night, I would fly over different homes.
I realised that when I fly in the spirit on your roof,
nothing will go well for you in your home.
My family rejected me because of all of these things.
I also realised that I was possessed, that I had spirits in me.
I used to visit the graveyard because I felt no fear towards anything.
I would visit the graveyard, the sea, at about 2:00am in the morning.
I would see dead people in the spirit and they would sometimes talk to me in the physical.
Whenever I go to the toilet to do the masturbation,
I would look at the mirror and the person inside of me shows himself through the mirror.
After masturbating, I would lick my sperms and I could wish for anything that I wanted.
Especially at the time when I was involved in online scamming,
I would call the names of the persons
and command them to send to me any amount of money.
Through that scamming, I deceived many people and stole money from them in many ways.
While I am typing on the computer and telling these people that I want them to send me money,
I would take part of my sperms and put them on the keyboard.
When I type, whatever I tell them they would obey.
I have been to many places for deliverance.
During this period, I talked to many girls on the internet.
The moment I send to you a friend request on Facebook and you accept,
you are automatically initiated.
I would continue to communicate with you, deceiving you, and convincing you
to go online live and have sex with me on camera.
I give most of these women appointment and meet with them physically.
You always invite them to have affair with you on the internet.
Yes, sir, that's true.
How?
I send them a friend request on the internet and I communicate with them,
trying to create a friendly relationship with them.
Afterwards, I extend to the sexual part of it like telling them to get naked
on camera and that we could have sex. I tell them how beautiful they are.
How many have you done that to?
There are many of them because I have thousands of friends on Facebook.
Can you see? My heart goes for your children.
Tell your neighbour, "My heart goes for your children".
Tell your neighbour again.
It takes concentration and commitment, and when you are into this business,
you cannot concentrate at all.
This is how you know that something is wrong.
After having sex with them on the internet, we masturbate and they get initiated.
They come and join us in the marine world.
Whenever I was scamming, I would masturbate, taste my sperms,
put them on the keyboard and I type. Whatever I tell you, you will obey.
I also came to realise that I had powers in my eyes to seduce girls.
I don't need to be with a girl for more than five minutes before having sex with her.
Five minutes is too much for me.
When I look at you in your eyes, I seduce you and have sex with you instantly.
Most of the girls that I had sex with were virgins.
After having sex with them, they would also be initiated into the marine kingdom.
I have destroyed many people and girls in my country.
In my hometown, everybody knows me as a bad person.
Whenever I am not there, the ladies would say negative things about me.
Whenever they see me, they can't say anything bad about me;
they would always say good things about me and love being around me.
I also had the spirit of anger that nobody could defeat me.
I could fight with eighteen people and defeat all of them. I was unbeatable.
I also eat about seven times in a day.
I eat in the morning about four times.
I could eat even more than seven times in a day.
I eat even at 3:00am, 4:00am, and during masturbation.
I could masturbate about eight times, constantly without resting.
When I have a blackout, I regain my energy and become stronger and more powerful.
I have gone to many places for deliverance.
I went to many churches for deliverance.
I went to three witch doctors for deliverance.
I talked to a witch doctor about the marine spirits
that were in me and that I wanted him to help me.
He did some sacrifices and later on came and told me that
the evil spirits are tormenting him and that I should go away.
When I was in his small apartment, I saw Emmanuel TV.
He had a flat screen TV in his apartment.
He left the house to buy some traditional herbs to prepare the rituals.
I took the remote control and changed the TV channels and I saw Emmanuel TV.
A voice spoke to me that I need to go to The SCOAN and get deliverance there.
I have been to many places; I have done all sorts of rituals,
I have eaten all sorts of things and done terrible things.
When I was possessed, I made my mother not to have anything at all.
I took all her money, everything, and made her a laughing stock in my family.
During my deliverance, Wise Man Racine prayed for me and I was delivered.
I feel better, strong, and my Christian life is improving by the grace of God.
I keep reading the Bible and praying to God to help me, to strengthen me to go along.
I am a Christian, a born-again now and I pray that God should help me
to improve my Christian life and not to go back to my past.
I cannot ever think of going back to my past.
I have a lot of friends that I introduced into scamming.
My advice to them is that they should quit from it immediately because
what they are doing is not natural, it is spiritual.
They need deliverance. I advice them to quit immediately and
go for deliverance for a total change in their lives.
Let them follow Christ because that lifestyle is not good at all.
My advice to them is that they should quit from it because that life is not good at all.
My name is Sally Williams, from Cameroon.
Before I met the father, I was a free girl, a prostitute.
Ok.
Don't worry, everything would be alright.